AFSCME, District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series V: General Files, 1944-2000.
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Sanitarians, Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1958-1966 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Sanitarians, Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1953-1960 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1961-1964 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): X-Ray Technicians, 1953-1954 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Local 924 (Laborers), 1962-May 1964 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Local 924 (Laborers), Jun 1964-Dec 1964 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Local 924 (Laborers), Jan 1965-Jul 1965 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Local 924 (Laborers), Aug 1965-1967, 1970-1976, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Certifications, 1959-1966, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Constitution and Bylaws, Membership/Dues Book, 1954; 1964 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Grievances, Jan 1964-Jun 1964 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Grievances, Jul 1964-Dec 1964 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Grievances, 1965-1966 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Grievances, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1962-1966 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals, formerly Local 154X), 1953-1959 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals), 1960-1962 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals), 1963-1966, 1970-1975, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Accounting Personnel, 1961-1966 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Accounting Personnel, Minutes, 1957-1959, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Grievances, 1957-1966 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1960-1966 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Minutes, 1961-1963 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Newsletters, 1974-1976, 1981-1982; 1989 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Printed Material on Housing Issues, undated, 1962-1964 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1957-1965 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators), 1963-1967; 1970-1976; 2000 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators): Grievances, 1960, 1963-1967 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Local 1062 (Supervisors of Automotive Plants and Equipment), 1965-1966, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Local 1070 (Court, County, and Department of Probation Employees): County Clerks, 1965-1966, 1971-1976, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Local 1070 (Court, County, and Department of Probation Employees): Court Reporters, 1955-1966, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Local 1070 (Court, County, and Department of Probation Employees): Judicial Conference and County Employees, 1965-1966, 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Local 1070 (Court, County, and Department of Probation Employees): Laborers, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Local 1113 (Department of Finance), 1958, 1966, 1970-1976 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Local 1157 (Department of Transportation Supervisory Employees): Highway and Sewer Foremen, 1967-1970 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Local 1189 (Psychologists), 1966-1967, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Local 1212 (Seasonal Park Men and Seasonal Park Helpers), 1966-1967, 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Local 1219 (Real Estate Employees), 1959-1965 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Local 1219 (Real Estate Employees), 1966-1967, 1970, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Local 1219 (Real Estate Employees): Constitution and Bylaws, 1962-1964 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Local 1219 (Real Estate Employees): Grievances, 1960-1967 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Local 1219 (Real Estate Employees): Minutes, 1959-1960, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Local 1251 (Board of Education Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1959-1963 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Local 1251 (Board of Education Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1964-1966 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Local 1251 (Board of Education Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Local 1251 (Board of Education Clerical-Administrative Employees): Grievances, 1963-1966 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Local 1251 (Board of Education Clerical-Administrative Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Local 1251 (Board of Education Clerical-Administrative Employees): Minutes, 1964, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Local 1251 (Board of Education Clerical-Administrative Employees): Printed Material, 1970-1976, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Local 1251 (Board of Education Clerical-Administrative Employees): Rules and Regulations, undated (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Local 1251 (Board of Education Clerical-Administrative Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1963-1964 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Local 1306 (American Museum of Natural History, AMNH, Attendant Guards), 1954-1958 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Local 1306 (AMNH), 1959-1965, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Local 1306 (AMNH): Grievances, 1958-1964 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Local 1306 (AMNH): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1957-1966 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - Local 1306 (AMNH): Minutes, 1959 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Local 1306 (AMNH): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1956-1964 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Local 1308 (Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority, TBTA, Sergeants and Lieutenants), 1958-1966, 1970-1972 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - Local 1308 (TBTA Sergeants and Lieutenants): Grievances, 1957-1965 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - Local 1308 (TBTA Sergeants and Lieutenants): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1960-1965 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Local 1320 (Sewage Treatment and Senior Sewage Treatment Workers, formerly Local 154G), 1956-1960 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Local 1320 (Sewage Treatment and Senior Sewage Treatment Workers), 1961-1962 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Local 1320 (Sewage Treatment and Senior Sewage Treatment Workers), 1963-1966, 1970-1971, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Local 1320 (Sewage Treatment and Senior Sewage Treatment Workers): Constitution and Bylaws, undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Local 1320 (Sewage Treatment and Senior Sewage Treatment Workers): Grievances, 1959-1966 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Local 1320 (Sewage Treatment and Senior Sewage Treatment Workers): Health and Safety Guide, 1981-1983 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Local 1320 (Sewage Treatment and Senior Sewage Treatment Workers): History, 1957-1982 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Local 1320 (Sewage Treatment and Senior Sewage Treatment Workers): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1959, 1964-1966 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Local 1320 (Sewage Treatment and Senior Sewage Treatment Workers): Minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Local 1320 (Sewage Treatment and Senior Sewage Treatment Workers): Newsletters, 1981-1982, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Local 1320 (Sewage Treatment and Senior Sewage Treatment Workers): Salary Appeal Briefs, undated, 1960-1964 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Local 1321 (Queens Library Guild), undated, 1967, 1970-1976 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Local 1321 (Queens Library Guild), 1980-1981, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Local 1322 (Department of Environmental Protection Supervisory Employees, formerly Local 1414F), 1956-1966 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Local 1322 (Department of Environmental Protection Supervisory Employees): Constitution and Bylaws, 1958, ca.1962 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Local 1322 (Department of Environmental Protection Supervisory Employees) Grievances, 1955-1962 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Local 1322 (Department of Environmental Protection Supervisory Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Local 1322 (Department of Environmental Protection Supervisory Employees): Minutes, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Local 1322 (Department of Environmental Protection Supervisory Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1956-1965 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Local 1331 (Department of Air Pollution Control), 1954-1965 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Local 1331 (Department of Air Pollution Control): Constitution and Bylaws, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Local 1331 (Department of Air Pollution Control): Grievances, 1956-1965 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Local 1331 (Department of Air Pollution Control): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1965 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Local 1331 (Department of Air Pollution Control): Minutes, 1957-1965 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Local 1331 (Department of Air Pollution Control): Salary Appeal Briefs, ca.1955-1965 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Local 1359 (Rent Regulation Services Employees), 1962-1963 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Local 1359 (Rent Regulation Services Employees), 1964-1967, 1970-1976 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Local 1359 (Rent Regulation Services Employees): Constitution and Bylaws, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Local 1359 (Rent Regulation Services Employees): Grievances, 1962-1967 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Local 1359 (Rent Regulation Services Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1962-1966 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Local 1359 (Rent Regulation Services Employees): Newsletters, 1971-1976, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Local 1359 (Rent Regulation Services Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1962-1964 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Local 1396 (TBTA), 1958-Jul 1964 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Local 1396 (TBTA), Aug 1964-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Local 1396 (TBTA): Grievances, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Local 1396 (TBTA): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Local 1396 (TBTA): Minutes, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Local 1396 (TBTA): Newsletters, "Rock-Span News", 1964-1966 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Local 1396 (TBTA): Newsletters, "Rock-Span News", 1971-1973 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Local 1396 (TBTA): President's Reports, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Local 1407 (Accountants, Statisticians, and Actuaries), 1960-1962 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Local 1407 (Accountants, Statisticians, and Actuaries), 1963-1966 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Local 1407 (Accountants, Statisticians, and Actuaries), 1967, 1970-1976, 1981-1982 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Local 1407 (Accountants, Statisticians, and Actuaries) (Oversize), 1965 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Local 1407 (Accountants, Statisticians, and Actuaries): Grievances, 1956-1967 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Local 1407 (Accountants, Statisticians, and Actuaries): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Local 1407 (Accountants, Statisticians, and Actuaries): Minutes, 1962-1965, 1971-1976, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Local 1414 (Water Plant Operators), 1970, 1975, 1981-1982 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Local 1455 (Traffic Employees), 1966, 1970, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Local 1457 (Juvenile Center), ca.1967, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Local 1482 (Brooklyn Library Guild), 1967, 1970-1976, 1981-1982 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees), 1966-1967, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Human Resources Administration Organizing Drive against SSEU, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Local 1501 (New York Zoological Society), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Local 1501 (New York Zoological Society): Strike at Bronx Zoo and Coney Island Aquarium, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Local 1503 (Metropolitan Museum of Art, MMA, formerly Local 135M), 1955-1957 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Local 1503 (MMA), 1960-1965, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Local 1503 (MMA), 1976, 1981, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Local 1503 (MMA): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1961-1966 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Local 1503 (MMA): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1955-1957 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Local 1505 (Attendants, Park Service Workers, City Park Workers, and Debris Removers, formerly Local 149B), 1956-1963 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Local 1505 (Attendants, Park Service Workers, City Park Workers, and Debris Removers), 1964-1967, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Local 1505 (Attendants, Park Service Workers, City Park Workers, and Debris Removers): Constitution and Bylaws, undated, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Local 1505 (Attendants, Park Service Workers, City Park Workers, and Debris Removers): Grievances, 1959-1962 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Local 1505 (Attendants, Park Service Workers, City Park Workers, and Debris Removers): Grievances, 1963-1967 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Local 1505 (Attendants, Park Service Workers, City Park Workers, and Debris Removers): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1962-1966 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Local 1505 (Attendants, Park Service Workers, City Park Workers, and Debris Removers): Minutes, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Local 1505 (Attendants, Park Service Workers, City Park Workers, and Debris Removers): Newsletters, 1966, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Local 1505 (Attendants, Park Service Workers, City Park Workers, and Debris Removers): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1954-1965 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Local 1506 (Department of Parks Climbers and Pruners, formerly Local 149L), 1956-1967, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Local 1506 (Department of Parks Climbers and Pruners): Grievances, 1956-1958 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Local 1506 (Department of Parks Climbers and Pruners): Grievances, 1959-1966 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Local 1506 (Department of Parks Climbers and Pruners): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Local 1506 (Department of Parks Climbers and Pruners): Salary Appeal Briefs, ca.1959-1964 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Local 1507 (Department of Parks Gardeners, formerly Local 149J), 1956-1967 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Local 1507 (Department of Parks Gardeners): Grievances, 1956-1957 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Local 1507 (Department of Parks Gardeners): Grievances, 1958-1967 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Local 1507 (Department of Parks Gardeners) Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Local 1507 (Department of Parks Gardeners): Minutes, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Local 1507 (Department of Parks Gardeners): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1956-1964 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Local 1508 (Uniformed Parks Supervisors, formerly Local 149H), 1956-1959 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Local 1508 (Uniformed Parks Supervisors), 1960-1962 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Local 1508 (Uniformed Parks Supervisors), 1963-1967, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Local 1508 (Uniformed Parks Supervisors): Constitution and Bylaws, undated (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Local 1508 (Uniformed Parks Supervisors): Grievances, 1956-1967 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Local 1508 (Uniformed Parks Supervisors): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Local 1508 (Uniformed Parks Supervisors): Minutes, 1955-1958 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Local 1508 (Uniformed Parks Supervisors): Salary Appeal Briefs, ca.1956-1964 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Local 1509 (Youth Board), undated, 1964-Jun-67 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Local 1509 (Youth Board), Jul-67-Dec 1967, 1970-1976 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Local 1509 (Youth Board): Grievances, 1965-1967 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Local 1509 (Youth Board): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1967 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Local 1509 (Youth Board): Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1960-1965 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1966-1968, 1976, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Contract, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Grievances, 1962-May 1966 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Grievances, Jun 1966-Dec 1966 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, undated, 1964-1966; 1981; 1993 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Minutes, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Printed Material, 1970-1972 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Printed Material, 1973-1976 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Printed Material, 1980-1984; 1989; 1997 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1960-1964 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Stress Management Workshop, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Local 1559 (American Museum of Natural History, AMNH, formerly Locals 154H and 1504), 1957-1965 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Local 1559 (AMNH): Grievances, 1958-1961 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Local 1559 (AMNH): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1959-1966 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Local 1559 (AMNH): Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Local 1559 (AMNH): Salary Appeal Briefs, undated, 1962-1963 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Local 1588 (Department of Parks Clericals): Meeting Notices, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees), 1959-1961 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees), 1962-1963 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees), 1964-1965 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees), 1970-1979, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees): Grievances, 1958-1965 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1963-1966 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees): Minutes, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1959-1965 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Local 1655 (Metropolitan Transit Authority, MTA, Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1955-1959 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1960 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1961-1963 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1964-1966, 1971-1976 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees), undated, 1979-1982 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees): Financial Reports, 1960-1963 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees): Grievances, 1960-1966 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees): Minutes, 1957-1960 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1960-1965 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Local 1665 (Museum of the City of New York, MCNY), 1959-1965, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Local 1665 (MCNY): Grievances, 1962-1965 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Local 1665 (MCNY): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1960-1964 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Local 1665 (MCNY): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1959-1965 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Local 1674 (Supervisors of Parks Operations), 1959-1966, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Local 1674 (Supervisors of Parks Operations): Grievances, 1961-1967 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Local 1674 (Supervisors of Parks Operations): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Local 1674 (Supervisors of Parks Operations): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1960-1964 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Local 1757 (Assessors, Appraisers, and Mortgage Analysts), 1962-1967, 1970-1975 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Local 1757 (Assessors, Appraisers, and Mortgage Analysts): Grievances, 1963-1966 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Local 1757 (Assessors, Appraisers, and Mortgage Analysts): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1963-1966 (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Local 1757 (Assessors, Appraisers, and Mortgage Analysts): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1963-1965 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Local 1759 (Consumer Affairs Inspectors), 1960-1967, 1971, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Local 1759 (Consumer Affairs Inspectors): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1963-1965 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Local 1759 (Consumer Affairs Inspectors): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1963-1964 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Local 1783 (Housing Authority Maintenance and Operations Employees), 1963 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1963-1964 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1965 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1966-1967 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees): Grievances, 1964-1966 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, Feb 1965-Sep 1965 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, Oct 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees): Minutes, 1963-1965, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1963, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Local 1792 (Custodial Supervisors): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Local 1795 (Maintenance Men), 1964-1965 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Local 1795 (Maintenance Men): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Local 1795 (Maintenance Men): Stationary Firemen, 1970-1976, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Local 1797 (Custodial Supervisors), 1962-1966 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Local 1797 (Custodial Supervisors): Printed Material, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Local 1930 (New York Public Library Guild), 1967, 1970-1976, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Local 1930 (New York Public Library Guild): Newsletters, 1970-1976; 1981-1982; 1989 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Local 1931 (TBTA Maintenance Employees), 1972, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Local 2021 (Off-Track Betting Corporation, OTBC), 1970-1979 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Local 2021 (OTBC), 1980-1982, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Local 2021 (OTBC): Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Local 2054 (College Assistants), 1970-1975, 1981-1982, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Local 2507 (Uniformed EMTs and Paramedics), 1975, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Local 2627 (Electronic Data Processing Personnel), 1973-1976, 1981-1982, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Local 2906 (Marine Workers): Printed Material, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Locals: Lists, 1962, [1973?] (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Memoranda: General, 1972-1976 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Municipal Credit Union, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Municipal Employees Legal Services Plan (MELS), undated, 1975-1976, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Municipal Labor Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - National Black Nurses Association, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - New Jersey Department of Labor and Industry Report: Upgrading Community Service Aides in a Public Housing Agency I, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - New Jersey Department of Labor and Industry Report: Upgrading Community Service Aides in a Public Housing Agency II, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - New York City Board of Education, 1961-1966 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - New York City Board of Education: Meeting Calendars, 1963-1965 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - New York City Board of Education: Press Releases, 1961-1962 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - New York City Board of Education: Salary Schedules, 1961-1963 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - New York City Board of Education: Summary of Citywide Reading Test Results, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - New York City Budget, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - New York City Budget, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - New York City Budget, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - New York City Budget, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 8)